Alfred J. Frueh
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Alfred J. Frueh papers
1904-1993
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Alfred J. Frueh
4.1 linear feet
The Alfred J. Frueh papers, 1904-1993, measure 4.1 linear ft., and consist of biographical information, correspondence, notes and writings, art work, printed material, and photographs documenting the noted caricaturist's personal life and professional career.
Biographical Note
Alfred J. Frueh (1880-1968) was best known for his caricatures of theater personalities that appeared in The New Yorker from 1925 through 1962. In addition, he was a cartoonist, illustrator, painter, designer of children's furniture and toys, pop-ups, and cut-outs.
Upon graduation from the Lima Business College in his native Lima, Ohio, Al Frueh (pronounced "free") began farming and working in his father's brewery. He moved to St. Louis to live with relatives, and from 1904-1908 worked in the art department of the St. Louis Post-Dispatch. Frueh's 1907 cartoon of Fritzi Scheff, published in the St. Louis Post Dispatch, so outraged the music-hall star that her St. Louis performance was cancelled and the attendant publicity made Frueh a celebrity.
Frueh traveled to Paris, London, Rome, Munich, Berlin, and Madrid in 1908 and 1909. During this period, he studied at various art schools in Paris, receiving instruction from Theophile Steinlen, Lucien Simon, Naudin, and Henri Matisse. Upon his return to the United States, Frueh settled in New York City. His tenure at The World was interrupted by a return trip to Europe lasting from late 1912 until late 1914. While abroad, he married Giuliette Fanciulli, whom he had met in New York. He remained with The World for another ten years, also producing other work for publication and exhibition. With a young family Frueh wanted a less hectic life so he decided to switch from a daily publication to a weekly one. Thus began his affiliation with a newly established periodical, The New Yorker. Frueh's work appeared in its 1925 debut issue until his retirement in 1962. Mostly he contributed caricatures for the theater section, but he also produced cover designs, illustrations, and on occasion wrote brief pieces for the "Talk of the Town" and "Notes and Comments" sections. In 1926 the Frueh moved his family to a farm in Sharon, Connecticut, where he seriously pursued a longstanding hobby of growing fruit and nut trees.
Alfred J. Frueh died in Sharon, Connecticut, in 1968, after a long illness.
Scope and Content Note
The Alfred J. Frueh papers, 1904-1993, measure 4.1 linear ft., and consist of biographical information, correspondence, notes and writings, art work, printed material, and photographs documenting the noted caricaturist's personal life and professional career.
Biographical information includes birth, marriage, and death certificates, biographical notes, employment contracts, obituaries, and legal papers concerning patents and license agreements for toy animals and sheet material sculpture. Also included is a 1993 audiocassette recording of Frueh's children reminiscing about their father.
Correspondence consists mainly of incoming letters with a small number of replies drafted by Frueh interfiled. Most of Frueh's surviving outgoing letters are addressed to Giuliette Fanciulli (whom he married in 1913), her parents and his sister Minnie Frueh. Many of the letters to Giuliette and family members are illustrated. Also included are a large number of greeting cards (mainly Christmas cards) containing original artwork, from friends, artists, writers and colleague. The correspondence concerns both personal and career matters. Notable correspondents are: George Gershwin, Robert Henri, Mr. and Mrs. Elie Nadelman, Eugene O'Neil; Walter and Magda Pach, New Yorker editor Harold Ross, and Alfred Stieglitz. Other letters document Frueh's interest in nut and fruit trees.
Among the notes and writings by Frueh are six notebooks of miscellaneous jottings. Also included with this series are notes of ideas for art work, lists of caricature sketches, lists of plays and their casts, and address books kept by Alfred and Giuliette Frueh and by Giuliette and her mother (8 volumes). Notes and writing by other authors consist of lists of caricature sketches, a poem by an unknown writer, and 13 short stories by "Joe" with 6 illustrations by Frueh.
Art work by Frueh comprises the largest series. It consists mainly of caricature sketches, mostly theatrical, but some political, and a few of himself, wife Giuliette, and personal friends. In addition, there are greeting cards, paper sculptures, pop-ups and cut-outs, prints, and water colors. Also included are various sketches, drawings, designs, and patterns for cartoons, book covers, greeting cards, lamp bases and a shade, magic squares, paper sculptures, sheet material sculpture, toy animals, and wallpaper.
Among the printed material are articles by and about Frueh; book covers and jackets, magazine covers, and invitations, announcements, and a program cover designed by Frueh; caricatures, cartoons, and illustrations by Frueh; exhibition catalogs and announcements of Frueh's solo and group shows; and miscellaneous items.
Photographs of people consist of a studio portrait and informal views of Alfred Frueh, circa 1940s and undated, and of his daughter Barbara as a young child, circa 1919. Photographs of art work by Frueh are of caricatures, lamp bases, paper sculptures, and toy animals.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six series:
Series 1: Biographical Information, 1909-1993, undated (Box 1; 0.1 linear ft.)
Series 2: Correspondence, circa 1909-1968, undated (Boxes 1-2 and OV 7; 1.15 linear ft.)
Series 3: Notes and Writings, circa 1912-1963, undated (Box 2; 0.25 linear ft.)
Series 4: Art Work, circa 1906-1961, undated (Boxes 2-3, 6 and OV 8-9; 1.5 linear ft.)
Series 5: Printed Material, 1904-1986, undated (Boxes 4-5, 6 and OV10-12; 0.9 linear ft.)
Series 6: Photographs, circa 1919-circa 1960s, undated (Box 5; 0.2)
Index Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following index terms. People, families and organizations are listed under "Subjects" when they are the topic of collection contents and under "Names" when they are creators or contributors.
Subjects:
New Yorker (New York, N.Y.: 1925)
Subjects-Topical:
Caricatures and cartoons; Magazine illustration; Actors -- Caricatures and cartoons; Caricaturists -- New York (State) -- New York; Cartoonists -- New York (State) -- New York; Illustrators -- New York (State) -- New York; Greeting cards
Types of Materials:
Works of art; Christmas cards; Drawings; Illustrated letters; Photographs; Sketches
Provenance
The Alfred J. Frueh papers were the gift of his children, Barbara Frueh Bornemann, Alfred J. Frueh, Jr., and Robert Frueh, in 1993 and 1997.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. research facility.
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Biographical Information, 1909-1993, undated, Series 1:; (Box 1; 0.1 linear ft.)
  - Audiocassette recording of Frueh's Children Reminiscing about their Father, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Biographical Notes, circa 1922, undated (Box 1)
  - Birth, Marriage, and Death Certificates, 1913-1973 (Box 1)
  - Employment Contracts, 1910, 1921 (Box 1)
  - Homes, 1920, undated (Box 1)
  - Obituaries, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Patents and License Agreement for Toy Animals and Sheet-Material Sculpture, 1917-1922, undated (Box 1)
  - Travel Documents, 1909-1914 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, circa 1909-1968, undated, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-2, OV 7; 1.15 linear ft.)
  Arranged alphabetically, correspondence consists mainly of incoming letters to Frueh, and some addressed to his wife, Giuliette; a small number of replies drafted by Frueh are interfiled. Most of Frueh's surviving outgoing letters are addressed to Giuliette Fanciulli (whom he married in 1913), her parents, and his sister Minnie Frueh. Many of the family letters, especially those written by Frueh during his time in Europe, are illustrated. In addition, Christmas cards are plentiful, with a high percentage containing original artwork by artist friends and acquaintances.
  - American Brotherhood - Ashton, 1926-1968, undated (Box 1)
    American Brotherhood, The National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc.
    Angell, Ernest and Katharine
    Arens, Egmont and Ruth
    Arens, Egmont and Camille David
    Armstrong, Consul General and Lady Margot Hanway
    Ashermann family
    Ashton, Leota
  - Baer - Butterworth, 1920-1967, undated (Box 1)
    Baer
    Bamberger, Mrs. Theron (see Perlman)
    Barton, Carlotta and Ralph
    Beaufoy-Lane, H. J. ("Beef") and Katie
    Bedaux, Charles E.
    Berthoud, Mary Lamson
    Berthoud, Mollie
    Bode, William A.
    Boordy Vineyard
    Booth, Edward T. and Mary Lena
    Boronda family
    Brady, Alice
    Brennan, Mr. and Mrs. Charles T.
    Brinkerhoff, Bob and Pat
    Brisbane, A.
    Brooklyn Botanic Garden
    Brown, Ned
    Buffano, Remo and Florence Koehler
    Butterworth, Pearl and Roddy
  - Carr - Cushman, 1919-1967, undated (Box 1)
    Carr, Gene, Helen, and Cleantha (see also: Weill)
    Casamajor, Louis
    Casey, Mr. and Mrs. Frank DeSales
    Cassel, Mr. and Mrs. John
    Cesare, Oscar
    Chaffee, Melzar and Naomi
    Chessman, Bill and Dorothy
    Cimino, Harry and Miriam
    Clarke, Paul
    Clarke, Steve
    Cobb, Frank I.
    Cobb, Margaret
    Columbia University
    Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station
    Conrey family
    Cornell, Gerry and Helen
    Costillo, Patience
    Craven, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas C.
    Crosby, Percy
    Crowninshield, Frank
    Cunningham, Cecil, Clara Tice, and Miriam
    Cushman, Nancy
  - Davis - Draper, 1927-1963, undated (Box 1)
    Davis, Harriet and Malcom
    Dayton, Fred and Helena
    DeCasseres, Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin
    Deton, Brownie and Cra
    Dick, Elsie
    Diederick, William Hunt
    Dieterich family
    Digges, Dudley and Mary
    Dirks, Helen and Rudie
    Draper, Dorcas
  - Eaton - Falls, 1915-1963, undated (Box 1)
    Eaton, Mal
    Elder, Arthur T.
    Elvin, Veda
    Encyclopedia Britannica
    Englehardt, Irma Selz
    Estrada, Luis and Nell
    Euheuph, Isaac low
    Ewing, Neal H.
    Fallouey, Emile and Jeanne
    Falls, Bedelia and Charles (relative of Frueh)
  - Fanciulli, Mr. and Mrs. Francesco (Giuliette Frueh's parents), circa 1913-1914 (Box 1)
  - Fanciulli, Giuliette (Mrs. Alfred Frueh), 1912-1913, (4 folders; see also: Frueh, Giulliette) (Box 1)
  - Ferris - Freeman, 1925-1950, undated (Box 1)
    Ferris, Mr. and Mrs.
    Fornaro, Carlo
    Forsyth, Cecil
    Fox, Albert W.
    Fox, Edith and Fontaine
    Freeman, Elizabeth and Margaret
  - Frueh, Giuliette (wife), 1914-1957, (2 folders; see also: Fanciulli, Giuliette) (Box 1)
  - Frueh, Minnie (sister), circa 1909-1913 (Box 1)
  - Frueh, Robert - Gussow, 1920-1963, undated (Box 1)
    Frueh, Robert (son)
    Fruhauft, Aline
    Galbraith, Catherine Atwater (Mrs. J. Kenneth)
    Gannett, Louis and Ruth
    Gauthier, Eva
    Gavit, John P.
    Gaylor family
    Genthe, Arnold
    Geraghty, Eva and Jim
    Gershwin, George
    Gibbs, Wolcott
    Gibson, Charles Dana
    Glackens, Edith
    Gomme, Florence and Laurence
    Grant, Walter Monroe and Mollie Higgins Smith
    Graves, Arthur H.
    Graves, C. Edward
    Greenstein
    Gropper, William and Sophie
    Gross, Milt
    Gussow, B.S. and D.
  - Haenigsen - Hull, 1920-1967, undated (Box 1)
    Haenigsen, Harry and Jeanette
    Hahn, Manuel and Nancy
    Halsey, Frank and Ieda
    Hanway, Margot (see: Armstrong)
    Harris, Oello and William
    Harting family
    Hartman, Bertram and Gusta
    Hawley, Mr. and Mrs. Hubert
    Hayes, Helen
    Hayes, William
    Hays, Olive
    Henderson, Clifford and Rafe
    Henri, Robert
    Herold, Dan
    Herriman, George
    Hollister, Paul
    Holt, Horace and Pamela
    Hom, Dora L.
    Hoover, Dorothy and Ellison
    Hoppé, E. O.
    Hull family
  - Ingersoll - Kurr, 1914-1963, undated (Box 1)
    Ingersoll, Ralph
    Jacobsen, Ethel Plummer and Norman (see also: Plummer)
    Johnston, Hattie Belle and William
    Jones, Henry
    Jones, Robert Edmund
    Kelsey, Jim
    Kelten, Mr. and Mrs. Maurice
    Koenig, John D.
    Kuhn, Walt, Vera, and Brenda
    Kurr, Louis
  - Lamarque - Lyman, 1924-1965, undated (Box 1)
    Lamarque, Abril
    Lambert, J. B.
    Larson, Dorothy H.
    Lawson, Kate Drain
    Lederman, Minna
    Lescaze, Mary and William
    Library of Congress
    Locher family
    Lowry, Glenn
    Lutz, Dorothy
    Lyman, Mr. and Mrs. Robert Hunt
  - MacDougall - Museum of the City of New York, 1915-1962, undated (Box 1)
    MacDougall, Sally
    MacGowan, Kate
    Mager, Bob
    Martin, John
    Massaquer, Conrado W.
    Maxwell, William
    McClure, H. H.
    Merrill, Flora and Kim
    Mestre, Alfred and Marie
    Meyers, Helen Bradbury
    Miller, Helen and Kenneth
    Minor, Bob and Lydia
    Monterey, Carlotta (see also: O'Neill)
    Moran, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Francis
    Morse, Howard and Reba
    Museum of the City of New York
  - Nadelman - Nut Tree Nurseries, 1927-1967, undated (Box 1)
    Nadelman, Elie and Viola
    Narodny, Ivan and Maria
    The Nation
    New York Public Library
    Nut Tree Nurseries
  - O'Malley - Opffer, 1921-1959, undated (Box 2)
    O'Malley, Frank and Grace
    O'Neill, Carlotta and Eugene (see also: Monterey)
    Opffer
  - Pach - Pulitzer, 1916-1965, undated (Box 2)
    Pach, Magda and Walter
    Pagent Book Co.
    Pascin, Jules
    Pemberton, Murdock
    Pennsylvania Nut Growers' Association
    Perlman, Phyllis (Mrs. Theron Bamberger)
    Philadelphia Art Alliance
    Philadelphia Museum of Art
    Philyss, N. Burton
    Pierce, John Burney, Jr.
    Plain and Fancy
    The Players
    Plummer, Ethel (see also: Jacobsen)
    Popini, Alexander and Alice
    Porter and Co., Inc.
    The Print Galleries
    Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr.
    Pulitzer, Ralph
  - Rammelkamp - Roth, 1910-1959, undated (Box 2)
    Rammelkamp, Julian S.
    Revue du Vrai et du Beau
    Reyher, Betty
    Riis, Roger William
    Ringe, Helen H.
    Robinson, Boardman and Sally
    Roché, Henri Pierre
    Rohn, Ray
    Ross, Charles G.
    Ross, Harold W.
    Roth, Herb
  - Schabelitz - Stieglitz, 1912-1963, undated (Box 2)
    Schabelitz, M. and R.F.
    Schwab, Arnold T.
    Sendamore, Rene
    The Seven Seas
    Shawn, William
    Smith, Helen
    Smith, Jim and Patricia Collinge
    Smith, Mollie Higgins (see: Grant)
    Sparks, Lucy Chase
    Speinack, Sam and Bella Cohen
    Spillman, Margaret
    Springarn, Arthur and Marion
    Stein, Marceau
    Sterrett, Cliff and Nan
    Stevenson, Adlai E.
    Stewart, Albert and Margaret
    Stieglitz, Alfred
  - Tangeman - Tyrrell, 1928-1961, undated (Box 2)
    Tangeman, John
    Taylor, Laurette
    Terry, Daisy E.
    Theatre Arts Magazine
    Tice, Clara
    Tyrrell, Henry
  - Ullman Manufacturing Company - Viafora, 1921-1939, undated (Box 2)
    Ullman Manufacturing Company
    Van Loon, Hendrik and Jimmie (Mrs. Van Loon)
    Venable, Mr. and Mrs. Reginald Sidney Hgh
    Viafora, Gina and Gianni
  - Wallace - Wynne, 1921-1960, undated (Box 2)
    Wallace, David
    Wallace, Ethel
    Walts, Frank
    Washer, Ben
    Webster family
    Weill, Cleanthe Carr (see also: Carr)
    Weitenkampf, F.
    Wells, H. G.
    Westerman, Harry F.
    Westport Community Art Association
    Wetteran, Margaret Chaplin
    Weyhe
    White, Florence D.
    White, Katharine S. and E. B.
    Wilson family
    Woods, Charles W. and Mabel
    Wortman, Denys and Hilda (see also: OV 7)
    Wright, Glenn C.
    Wylie, Philip and Sally
    Wynne family
  - Young - Zorach; Unknown and Illegible, 1918-1968, undated (Box 2)
    Young, Art
    Young, Marjorie and Roland
    Zigrosser, Carl
    Zorach, Marguerite and William
    Unknown and Illegible
- Notes and Writings, circa 1912-1963, undated, Series 3:; (Box 2; 0.25 linear ft.)
  The series is organized 2 subseries:
  3.1: By Frueh, circa 1912-1963, undated
  3.2: By Others, 1933, undated
  - By Frueh, circa 1912-1963, undated, Subseries 3.1:
    - Address Books, circa 1920s-1940s, undated, (8 volumes in 2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Lists of Caricature Sketches, undated (Box 2)
    - List of Plays and the Actors, undated (Box 2)
    - Notebooks (6 vols.), circa 1912-1963, undated (Box 2)
    - Notes - Ideas for Art Work, undated (Box 2)
    - Notes, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
  - By Others, 1933, undated, Subseries 3.2:
    - Lists of Caricature Sketches (A-Z), undated (Box 2)
    - Poem, "Gaspard et Zoé" by Unknown, undated (Box 2)
    - Short Stories (13) by Joe with Illustrations (6) by Frueh, 1933 (Box 2)
- Art Work, circa 1906-1961, undated, Series 4:; (Boxes 2-3, 6, OV 8-9; 1.5 linear ft.)
  The majority of art work by Frueh consists of caricatures sketches. These are mainly of theatrical figures, but also include some politicians (primarily those participating in the Teapot Dome/Sinclair Oil trials, 1923-1929), and a small number of himself, Giuliette, and friends. Most caricature sketches are in pencil; many are on tracing paper, and the reverse sides those on drawing paper/brown paper frequently are covered with graphite for the purpose of transfer or making multiple copies. Caricatures are filed alphabetically by name, and those featuring several cast members are filed by play title. Additional art work by Frueh includes cartoons, drawings, pop-ups and cut-outs, greeting cards, watercolors; also, there are designs and patterns for lamp bases and shades, magic squares, paper scuplture, sheet metal sculptures and toy animals. Art work by others consists of several caricatures of Frueh.
  In addition, Correspondence (Series 2) includes illustrated letters by Frueh and others. Most of those illustrated by Frueh date from his extended stays in Europe and are addressed to fiancé Giuliette Fanciulli and family members. There are also many Christmas cards and other greeting cards with original art work sent to Frueh by artist friends.
  4.1: By Frueh, 1920-1962, undated
  4.2: By Others, undated
  - By Frueh, 1920-1962, undated, Subseries 4.1:
    - Caricatures, Abel - Astor, undated (Box 2)
      Abel, Walter
      Adair, Jean
      Adams, Edith
      Adams, Joe
      Adams, Franklin P.
      Adler, Dr. Felix
      Adler, Stella
      Alberghetti, Anna Maria
      Albertson, Jack
      Allers, Franz
      Ameche, Don
      Anders, Glen
      Anderson, Judith (see also: Box 6)
      Andrews, Julie (see: Box 6)
      Andrews, Nancy
      Arden, Eve (see: Box 6)
      Arliss, George
      Arthur, Jean
      Astor, Vincent
    - Caricatures, Bailey - Bayes, undated (Box 2)
      Bailey, Judge
      Bailey, Pearl
      Bainter, Fay
      Bancroft, Anne
      Bankhead, Tallulah
      Barrymore, Ethel (see also: Box 6)
      Barrymore, John
      Barton, James
      Bayes, Norah
    - Caricatures, Beal - Brayard, undated (Box 2)
      Beal, John
      Bean, Orson
      Becher, John C.
      Belafonte, Harry
      Bel Geddes, Barbara
      Bell, Representative of Georgia
      Bellamy, Ralph
      Ben-Ami, Jacob
      Bernard, Tristam
      Berry, Eric
      Bigley, Isabel (see: Box 6)
      Blaine, Vivian
      Bloom, Claire
      Bond, Sheila
      Bond, Sudie
      Booth, Shirley (see also: Di Luca, Dino and Shirley Booth)
      Borah, W. E., Senator of Idaho
      Borge, Victor
      Bosley, Tom
      Brando, Marlon (see: Tandy, Jessica, with Marlon Brando, Karl Malden, and Kim Hunter)
      Brayard, Buck
    - Caricatures, Breckenidge - Cassilly, undated (Box 2)
      Breckenridge
      Brennan, Eileen
      Brisbane, Arthur
      Brooks, David
      Brossett, Collette and Pierre Olaf
      Brown, C. D.
      Brown, Pamela
      Bryant, Michael
      Brynner, Yul
      Buckmaster, John
      Buloff, Joseph
      Bunnage, Avis (see also: "The Hostage")
      Burns, David
      Burton, Norma
      Burton, Richard
      Calder, King
      Calder, Senator
      Calloway, Cab
      Cameron, Mitchell (see: Dunnock, Mildred, with Mitchell Cameron and Arthur Kennedy)
      Cantor, Eddie
      Caraway, Senator of Arkansas
      Carey, Joyce
      Carnovsky, Morris
      Carradine, John
      Carroll, Leo
      Caruso, Enrico
      Casamajor, Louis, M.D.
      Cassilly, Richard
    - Caricatures, Chalmers - Conway, 1920-1959, undated (Box 2)
      Chalmers, Thomas
      Channing, Carol
      Chaplin, Charlie
      Chase, Ilka
      Chavez
      Christians, Mandy
      Clark, Bobby
      Clark, Dane
      Clark, Ernest
      Clarke, Ina
      Clarke, Ina and Osgood Perkins
      Clayton, Jan
      Clayton, Senator of Alabama
      Clift, Montgomery
      Cobb, Lee J.
      Coe, John H.
      Cohen, George M.
      Coleman, Nancy
      Collier, Constance
      Collinge, Patricia
      Comden, Betty
      Conklin, Peggy
      Conners, Fingy, New York State Boss
      Connor, Joe
      Conroy, Frank
      Conway, Shirl
    - Caricatures, Cook - Cushman, undated (Box 2)
      Cook, Barbara
      Cook, Donald
      Cooke, Levi
      Cookson, Peter
      Coolidge, Philip
      Cooper, Gladys
      Cooper, Jackie
      Cornell, Helen
      Cornell, Katharine (see also: Box 6)
      Coularis, George
      Cowan, Jerome
      Coward, Noel
      Cowl, Jane
      Crews, Laura Hope
      Croy, Homer
      Culver, Roland
      Cummings, Vicki
      Curtis, Senator of Kansas
    - Caricatures, Dancers (Miner) - De Wolf, circa 1926-1962, undated (Box 2)
      Dancers (Miner)
      Dancing Figures (Josephine Premice)
      Daniels, David
      Daniels, Josephus, Senator of South Carolina
      Daniels, William
      Da Silva, Howard
      Davis, Bette
      Davis, Ossie
      Dawson, Anthony
      Day, Marilyn
      "A Death in the Family" (Colleen Dewhurst, Arthur Hill, and Aline McMahon)
      Decker, Albert
      Decker, Albert and Paul Scofield
      Dee, Ruby
      Delysia, Alice
      Denby, Edwin, Former Secretary of the Navy (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Denton, Crahan
      Derr, Richard
      Desky, Donald
      Desmond, Johnny
      Dewhurst, Colleen (see also: "A Death in the Family")
      De Wolf, Billy
    - Dhery - Drew, circa 1926-1956, undated (Box 2)
      Dhery, Robert and Colette Brossett
      Dhiegh, Kigh
      Digges, Dudley
      Digges, Dudley and Peter Holden
      Dillman, Bradford
      Di Luca, Dino
      Di Luca, Dino and Shirley Booth
      Ditrichstein, Leo
      Dixon, Jean
      Dohoney, Robert (Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Donahue, Jack
      Douglas, Melvyn
      Douglass, Stephen
      Dowling, Eddie
      Dowling, Eddie and Laurette Taylor
      Drake, Alfred
      Dranem
      Draper, Ruth
      Dressler, Marie
      Drew, John
    - Caricatures, Duncan - Ewell, undated (Box 2)
      Duncan, Todd
      Dunnock, Mildred
      Dunnock, Mildred, with Mitchell Cameron and Arthur Kennedy
      Durant, Jack
      Durante, Jimmy
      Eames, Clair
      Edeson, Robert
      Eldridge, Florence
      Eltinge, Julian
      Emerson, Faye (see also: Box 6)
      Emery, John
      Emhardt, Robert
      Enesco
      Epsine
      Erickson, Leif
      Evans, Maurice
      Evans, Michael
      Evelyn, Judith
      Ewell, Tom
    - Fabray - Foy, 1947, undated (Box 2)
      Fabray, Nanette
      Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial (see: Teapot Dome/Fall-Sinclair Oil Trial)
      Fassett, Jay
      Fay, Frank
      Faye, Joey
      Fenwick, Irene
      Ferrer, José
      Ferrer, Mel
      Fickett, Mary
      Field, Betty
      Field, Virginia
      Fisk, Minnie Maddern
      Fisk, Minnie Maddern and Walter Fitzgerald
      Fitzgerald, Walter (see: Fisk, Minnie Maddern and Walter Fitzgerald)
      Flanders, Michael
      Flemying, Robert
      Fletcher, Bramwell
      Fonda, Henry